livingkool.com 2019-05-12

# Living Kool - Daily Deals, Things to Do Dubai Privacy Policy

“All credit/debit cards details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties”. Your personal information is stored by LIVING KOOL for the purpose of sending email about the daily deals that LIVING KOOL brings to its subscribers, and also to confirm/verify the process of payments for the vouchers purchased by the subscriber/user at LIVING KOOL. Your personal information is safe with LIVING KOOL, and we will not disclose, rent, share or sell any subscriber/user information with any Third Party that is not affiliated or partners/merchants of LIVING KOOL. Your personal information will also be used to better understand the requirement of LIVING KOOL & its’ subscribers/users in order to bring you the best deals in town. 

### Requirement & Information

Requirement   
LIVING KOOL Users/Subscribers are only eligible to register/subscribe/transact at LIVING 

Personal Information, Email & Privacy Policy   
Your personal information is stored by LIVING KOOL for the purpose of sending email about the daily deals that LIVING KOOL brings to its subscribers, and also to confirm/verify the process of payments for the vouchers purchased by the subscriber/user at LIVING KOOL. Upon registration you will receive emails from LIVING KOOL about LIVING KOOL Daily Deals, Newsletters, marketing emails on behalf of LIVING KOOL merchant promotions & events. Your personal information is safe with LIVING KOOL, and we will not disclose any subscriber/user information with any Third Party that is not affiliated or in business with LIVING KOOL. Your personal information will also be used to better understand the requirement of LIVING KOOL & its’ subscribers/users in order to bring you the best deals in town. The user/subscriber can unsubscribe from such emails at any time from the links provided within the email, to stop receiving any further emails which may take up to 2-3 working days to be in effect. 

Legal Disclaimer   
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when required to protect the LIVING KOOL rights, protect the safety & security of other users/subscribers to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on LIVING KOOL. 

Links   
– LIVING KOOL contains links to other websites. Please be aware that LIVING KOOL is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users/subscribers to be aware when they leave LIVINGKOOL and read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by LIVING KOOL. 

Policy Amendment   
LIVING KOOL has the right to amend the Terms & Conditions and its policy on this page at any time which will be effective at the same time of amendment, and will accordingly inform the Users/Subscribers on the main page of LIVING KOOL or via an email. 

Fees & Charges   
There is no fees charged to subscribe/register at LIVING KOOL, except for the purchase of vouchers through Credit/Debit Card. 

User Equipment   
User/Subscriber shall be wholly and solely responsible for their equipment & charges related to those equipment used to access LIVING KOOL. LIVING KOOL will not be responsible for any damage or loss to the User/Subscriber’s equipment resulting from the use of LIVING KOOL. 

Copyright & Trademarks   
Everything located on or in LIVING KOOL, including the Microsites, is the exclusive property of LIVING KOOL or used with express permission of the copyright and/or trademark owner. Any copying, distributing, transmitting, posting, linking, deep linking, or otherwise modifying of LIVING KOOL or any of the Microsites without the express written permission of LIVING KOOL is strictly prohibited. Trademarks & Logos displayed at LIVING KOOL are a trade mark of LIVING KOOL, which is either produced/developed by LIVING KOOL &/or its partners/businesses that are promoted at LIVING KOOL. Any unauthorized use of the content of this website or violation of this policy may result in a copyright, trademark or other intellectual property right infringement that may subject you to civil and/or criminal penalties. 

SSL   
LIVING KOOL is a secured website using an SSL (Secured Socket Layer) & a secure payment gateway to ensure that your personal & sensitive information is safe as it is transmitted to us through an encryption. Unfortunately, no data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. But we do best to take all security measures to its maximum to avoid any such loss of information. 

Refunds   
We always want our customers to be happy. But LIVING KOOL is not responsible for any quality of product or service from the merchant. There is no refund on any vouchers purchased, unless the merchant refuses to accept any valid voucher. Invalid/Expired vouchers are non-refundable, and no voucher is valid for exchange of cash. Refund policy would only take place in unforeseen situations it would be either Cash/credit Card refund or Shopping credits In your account. 

Credit/Debit Card Usage   
Please ensure that the purchase of vouchers through Credit/Debit Card is with your own Credit/Debit Card using your own LIVING KOOL account, and not a Third Party Credit/Debit Card and/or a Third Party LIVING KOOL account. Any purchase that is done through a Third Party Credit/Debit Card and/or a Third Party LIVING KOOL account, will entail to invalidation of a voucher purchased through that Account/Card at any time, and no refunds will be offered by LIVING KOOL. 

Cash On Delivery   
Cash on Delivery is not available at the time, but will be introduced soon. 

Support   
For any further queries or clarifications please send us an email at support@livingkool.com 

Cancelation policy   
Please refer to Refund Policy 

Delivery policy   
Voucher would be sent to your email address once The deal has been purchased for product delivery A third party courier company would provide this service.
